afinedirectory.com 2009-03-24

# A Fine Directory- Privacy Policy AFineDirectory.Com

## A Fine Directory Privacy Policy

In order to provide a safe and secure environment in our web site, AFINEDIRECTORY.Com, we have created this statement dedicated to the Privacy Policy, which is subject to change without notice. It is recommended that you review this Privacy Policy regularly.

### PinBy.Com & COOKIES

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. AFINEDIRECTORY.Com sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our visitors more. We do not disclose cookies that collected by AFINEDIRECTORY.Com to other third parties.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

It is optional to register an account to submit your site to be considered for inclusion in our directory. No matter submitting sites or registering an account, the only personal information we gather are your name, e-mail and URL you provided. We use such information in connection with the provision of AFINEDIRECTORY.Com only, and we do not redistribute your information to other parties.

When you sponsor our service, you may be required to provide us with your billing information, such as name, email, address, and your credit card details. We may use this information to inform you about the status of your order, as well as to let you know about upcoming PinBy.Com services. Tracking of user activity on our site is solely for internal purposes in order to provide you with the best possible experience. We do not share your information with other third parties.

When you access our site, AFINEDIRECTORY.Com, your information such as IP address, platform, browser, date and time are automatically stored for traffic analysis purpose. We do not disclose your personally identifiable data to other third parties.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

AFINEDIRECTORY.Com collects links to other web sites. Please be aware that we can not be held responsible for the privacy practices and content of such web sites listed in our site.

### MORE INFORMATION

For any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please [Contact Us](http://www.afinedirectory.com/contact.php).
